Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General Accounting, 1957-1974; MS2061 Series 3
  - Bank Checks, Aug.-Dec., First National Bank, 025339 1, School, 1972 (Box 213, Folder 2029)
  - Bank Checks, Sept.-Oct., First National Bank, 026691 4, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 213, Folder 2030)
  - Bank Checks, Oct.-Nov., First National Bank, 0252565, 1972 (Box 213, Folder 2031)
  - Bank Checks, Nov.-Dec., First National Bank, 0266914, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 2032)
  - Bank Checks, Dec., First National Bank, 025 256 5, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 2033)
  - Bank Checks, Union Trust, 3 057 860, 1972 (Box 214, Folder 2034)
  - Bank Checks, Suburban Trust Company, 54 208 4, 1972-1973 (Box 214, Folder 2035)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Feb., First National Bank, 0252565, 1973 (Box 214, Folder 2036)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Feb., First National Bank, 026 691 4, Subscriptions, 1973 (Box 215, Folder 2037)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-May, District of Columbia National Bank, 600 221 8. School, 1973 (Box 215, Folder 2038)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-May, First National Bank, 025 339 1, 1973 (Box 215, Folder 2039)
  - Bank Checks, Mar., First National Bank, 025 256 5, 1973 (Box 215, Folder 2040)
  - Maryland IncomeTax, Washington Drama Center, 1958 (Box 216, Folder 2041)
  - D.C. FranchiseTax, Washington Drama Center, 1958 (Box 216, Folder 2042)
  - Federal IncomeTax, Washington DramaC enter, 1959 (Box 216, Folder 2043)
  - D.C. FranchiseTax, Washington Drama Center, 1959 (Box 216, Folder 2044)
  - D.C. Sales Tax Exemption Instructions, 1959 (Box 216, Folder 2045)
  - Maryland Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1959 (Box 216, Folder 2046)
  - Federal Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2047)
  - Federal Excise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2048)
  - Federal Unemployment Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2049)
  - D.C. Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2050)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, Washington Theater Club, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2051)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2052)
  - Maryland Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 216, Folder 2053)
  - Federal Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2054)
  - Federal Excise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2055)
  - Federal Admissions Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2056)
  - Federal Unemployment Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2057)
  - D.C. Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2058)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1961 (Box 216, Folder 2059)
  - 1961 Maryland Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, undated (Box 216, Folder 2060)
  - Federal Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2061)
  - Federal Excise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2062)
  - D.C. Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2063)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2064)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2065)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, Washington Theater Club & Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2066)
  - Maryland Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1962 (Box 217, Folder 2067)
  - Federal Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2068)
  - Federal Income Tax, Washington Theater Club, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2069)
  - Federal Excise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2070)
  - Federal Sales Tax, Washington Theater Club, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2071)
  - D.C. Income Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2072)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2073)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2074)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 217, Folder 2075)
  - Federal Income Tax, Washington Theater Club, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 2076)
  - Federal Excise Tax, Washington Drama Center, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 2077)
  - D.C. Income Tax, Washington Theater Club, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 2078)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, Washington Theater Club, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 2079)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 2080)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1964 (Box 218, Folder 2081)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 2082)
  - Federal Excise Tax, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 2083)
  - D.C. Income Tax, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 2084)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 2085)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1965 (Box 218, Folder 2086)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2087)
  - Federal Income Tax Exemption, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2088)
  - D.C. Income Tax, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2089)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2090)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2091)
  - D.C. Sales Tax Exemption, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2092)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1966 (Box 218, Folder 2093)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1967 (Box 219, Folder 2094)
  - Federal Tax Change in Accounting Period to End Sept. 30,1967 (Box 219, Folder 2095)
  - Federal Unemployment Tax, 1967 (Box 219, Folder 2096)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1967 (Box 219, Folder 2097)
  - D.C. Real Estate Tax, 1967 (Box 219, Folder 2098)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1968 (Box 219, Folder 2099)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1968 (Box 219, Folder 2100)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1969 (Box 219, Folder 2101)
  - D.C. D.C.Franchise Tax, 1969 (Box 220, Folder 2102)
  - D.C. Sales Tax Opposition, 1969 (Box 220, Folder 2103)
  - Unemployment Tax, 1969 (Box 220, Folder 2104)
  - Maryland Income Tax, 1969 (Box 220, Folder 2105)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 2106)
  - D.C. Taxes Personal Property Tax, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 2107)
  - D.C. Franchise Tax, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 2108)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 2109)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1971 (Box 221, Folder 2110)
  - Federal Unemployment Tax, 1971 (Box 221, Folder 2111)
  - D.C. Income Tax, 1971 (Box 221, Folder 2112)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, 1971 (Box 221, Folder 2113)
  - D.C. Sales Tax, 1971 (Box 221, Folder 2114)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1971 (Box 221, Folder 2115)
  - Maryland Income Tax, 1971 (Box 222, Folder 2116)
  - Virginia Income Tax, 1971 (Box 222, Folder 2117)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2118)
  - Federal Unemployment Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2119)
  - D.C. Income Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2120)
  - D.C. Personal Property Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2121)
  - D.C. Sales Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2122)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2123)
  - Maryland Income Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2124)
  - Virginia Income Tax, 1972 (Box 222, Folder 2125)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1973 (Box 222, Folder 2126)
  - D.C. Unemployment Tax, 1973 (Box 222, Folder 2127)
- Artwork, audio tapes, and record albums, 1960-1970; MS2061 Series 4
  This series contains artwork, audio tapes, and record albums. The material dates from 1960-70.
  These materials consisting of unidentified material, duplicates of artwork, and individual items that did not fit into the other series. There are also audio tapes, which are in no established order, and phonograph records. The records are mostly 33 1/3 RPM albums, arranged roughly by size and country of origin. The music ranges from popular tunes to folk songs.
  - Misc.1, undated (Box 223, Folder 2128)
  - Misc.2, undated (Box 223, Folder 2129)
  - Misc.3, undated (Box 223, Folder 2130)
  - Duplicates - Exhibit use, undated (Box 223, Folder 2131)
  - Washington Theater Club Highlights, undated (Box 224, Folder 2132)
  - John Wentworth Checks and deposits (may not be Theater Club related), undated (Box 224, Folder 2133)
  - Howie (electrical code), undated (Box 224, Folder 2134)
  - Equipment for L St., 1969-1970 (Box 224, Folder 2135)
  - Subscriber's complaints, undated (Box 225, Folder 2136)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 225, Folder 2137)
  - Telephone extensions - Both theaters, undated (Box 225, Folder 2138)
  - Guest book, 1960-1962 (Box 225, Folder 2139)
  - The International Folk Singers with Orchestra - Hava Nagila London, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 1)
  - Doug Clark and the Hot Nuts On Campus - - Gross 102, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 2)
  - John Salisbury - A Message for Americans - Monaural, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 3)
  - David Shoenbrun - Who's Right in Vietnam?, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 4)
  - Louie, Louie - The Kingmen Wand - 657, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 5)
  - Roger Williams - Summer Wind Kapp KS 3434, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 6)
  - SSgt Barry Sadler - Ballads of the Green Berets - RCA Victor LSP 3547, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 7)
  - Boston Pops Arthur Fielder - Tenderly - RCA Victor - LSC 2798, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 8)
  - Netanai Davarth - Yiddish Folk Songs - Vangarud - VSD 2127, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 9)
  - Frankie Carle - Great Piano Hits - RCA Victor - LSP 3425, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 10)
    Scope and Contents
    Note there is no item 11
  - Lou Christie - Lightiiiii' Strikes - CSJ 298, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 12)
  - Nancy Sinatra - Boots --First SFL 1343, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 13)
  - Paul Revere and The Raiders - Kicks - Tongsheng- MXL 1082, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 14)
  - Andy Williams - Love, Andy Leico - PLS 3244, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 15)
  - Johnny Mathiu - My Name is Johnny CSJ 159, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 16)
  - The Beach Boys Today - Please let me wonder--China Record, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 17)
  - The Monkees - Saturday's Child Record SWL 1034, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 18)
  - Blood Sweat & Tears - Variations on a theme by Eric Satie First - FL-S 1601, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 19)
  - The Ventures- Best of the Ventures HS 297, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 20)
  - The Rolling Stones - Mother's little helper First FL 1297, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 21)
  - Peter, Paul, and Mary in Concert Le Deserteur Stereophonic - TWL 1121, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 22)
  - The Lovin' Spoonful - Do you believe in Magic Ceico - PLS 3087, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 23)
  - West Side Story - Prologue Stereophonic - TWL 1042, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 24)
  - Sing of our Times The Brothers Four - Four Strong Winds Hae Shan HS 250, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 25)
  - Cream Wheels of Fire Live at the Fillmore - Crossroads First FL 1630, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 26)
  - The Best of the Top Song - Hair LM 2284, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 27)
  - Bee Gees - Bee Gees 1st CSJ 803, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 28)
  - Johnny Rivers - Whiskey a Go-Go Revisted Tonsheng - MXL 1213, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 29)
  - Blood, Sweat & Tears - Overture First - FL 1601, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 30)
  - Herman's Hermits - I'm into something good - MGM -E 4282, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 31)
  - 1812 - Wellington's Victory SRD 19, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 32)
  - Doug Clark & the Hot Nuts - Nuts To You - Gross Records Co. GR 101, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 33)
  - The Lovin' Spoonful Do You Believe in Magic, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 34)
  - Peter, Paul, and Mary in Concert, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 35)
  - Sandy Baron & Joan Rivers Little Mozart Sure Records - S 107, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 36)
  - Top Tunes Vol. 3 Joy - J 50103, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 37)
  - Ray Stevens and others Harry the Harry Ape Liming Records - LM 227, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 38)
  - Cliff Richard and others Summer Holiday Liming Records - LM 224, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 39)
  - The New Vaudeville Band an others Win Chester Cathedral Universal- UHM 105, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 40)
  - Connie Francis and others Second Hand Love Universal - UHM 40, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 41)
  - Claude King and others Wolverton Mountain Universal - UHM 41, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 42)
  - Brenda Lee and others Losing You Universal- UHM 52, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 43)
  - Esses and others Easier Said Than Done Universal - UHM 55, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 44)
  - Beatles and others Can't Buy Me Love Universal - UHM 70, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 45)
  - Mary Wells and others My Guy Universal - UHM 71, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 46)
  - Bobby Vinton and others Tell Me Why Universal - UHM 72, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 47)
  - Elvis Presley and others Crying On The Charel Universal - UHM 84, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 48)
  - Beatles and others Ticket to Ride Universal - UHM 84, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 49)
  - Four Tops and others Can't Help Myself Universal - UHM 85, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 50)
  - James Brown and others It's a Man's Man's World Universal - UHM 98, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 51)
  - The Everly Brothers and others Crying In the Rain ANL 628, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 52)
  - The Tokens and others The Lion Sleeps Tonight Tai Shen - AK 648, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 53)
  - Larry Verne and others Mr. Custer, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 54)
  - The Monkees and othes Valleri Universal - UHM 120, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 55)
  - The Young Rascals and others Grooving Universal - UHM 111, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 56)
  - Petula Clark and othes This is My Song Universal - UHM 108, undated; Series 4 (Box 226, Item 57)
  - Johnny Rivers and others Poor Side of Town Universal - UHM 104, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 58)
  - Seekers and others Georgy Girl Universal- UHM 106, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 59)
  - Buckinghams and others King of A Drag Universal - UHM 107, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 60)
  - Four Sea Sons and others Candy Girl Liming Records - LM 228, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 61)
  - The Beatles Thank You Girl PPL 1103, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 62)
  - Four Pops and others Reach Out, I'll Be There Universal UHM 103, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 63)
  - The Happenings and others See You In September Universal - UHM 102, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 64)
  - Loving Spoonful and others Summer in the City Universal - UHM 101, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 65)
  - Frank Sinatra and others Strangers in the Night Universal - UHM 100, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 66)
  - Beatles and others Paperback Writer Universal - UHM 99, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 67)
  - Gene Chandler and other Duke of Earl Wu Chou - L 619, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 68)
  - Kingston Trio Here We Go Again Ace Records - AR APS 10 6020, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 69)
  - Johnny Horton's Memories Wu Chou Records - GL 49, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 70)
  - Connie Francis and others Second Hand Love Queen Record - QNL 8519, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 71)
  - Lee Dorsey and others Do-Re-Mi Queen Record - QNL 8503, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 72)
  - Duane Eddy's Great Hits 20th Century Records - TL 335, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 73)
  - Paul Anka Hit -10 Paramount Record - PPL 1040, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 74)
  - The Tokens and others The Lion Sleeps Tonight, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 75)
  - Tom Giazer and others On Top of Spaghetti Liming Record - LM 226, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 76)
  - Connie Francis and others If My Pillow Could Talk Liming Record - LM 225, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 77)
  - The Rocky Fellers and others "Killer Joe" Liming Record - LM 223, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 78)
  - Lou Christie and others Two Faces Have I Liming Record - LM 220, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 79)
  - Chubby Checker and others Let's Limbo Some More Liming Record - LM 216, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 80)
  - Spencer Ross and others Tracy's Theme Universal UHM NO. 1, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 81)
  - Elvis Presley and others I Gotta Know Unviersal - UHM no. 10, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 82)
  - The Shirelles and others Will You Love Me Tomorrow Universal - UHM No. 13, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 83)
  - Elvis Presley and others Lonely Man Universal - UHM No. 14, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 84)
  - Brook Benton and others Think Twice Universal - UHM no. 16, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 85)
  - Jerry Butler and others Find Another Girl Universal - UHM No. 17, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 86)
  - Elvis Presley and others I Feel So Bad Universal - UHM No. 20, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 87)
  - Elvis Presley and others Wild in the Country Universal - UHM No. 22, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 88)
  - Johnny Burnette and others God, Country and My Baby Universal - UHM No. 30, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 89)
  - Connie Francis and others Teach Me How to Twist Universal - UHM No. 37, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 90)
  - Elvis Presley and others Good Luck Charm Universal - UHM No. 38, undated; Series 4 (Box 227, Item 91)
  - Tape of Josephine Cockrell Thornton, undated; reel to reel tape (Box 227, Reel 1)
  - Seven at a Blow (master tape), undated; reel to reel tape (Box 227, Reel 2)
  - NYC Shakespeare Festival AMRAM The Tempest, undated; reel to reel tape, 7 1/2 ips copy, monaural (Box 227, Reel 3)
  - Josquin des Pres Misa Dux Ferrarie Guillaumede Machant Ballads Virilais Rondeaux, undated; reel to reel tape, full track- 1200' 7.5 speed 1/2 hour (Box 227, Reel 4)
  - Voice of America interview Davey Marlin-Jones, 1967 March 13; Series 4 (Box 230, Reel 1)
  - Voice of America interview Davey Marlin-Jones, director and John Hillerman, actor, 1967 March 28; Series 4 (Box 230, Reel 2)
    General
    interview by Jeanne M. Marshall at 7.5 ips
  - Voice of America interview Davey Marlin-Jones, 1968 March 8; Series 4 (Box 230, Reel 3)
    7.5 ips For: JM Marshall
  - Voice of America interview Washington Theater Club's Teenage Theater, 1968 May 14; Series 4 (Box 230, Reel 4)
    ap 30' 7.5 ips
  - Voice of America interview Washington Theater Club's Teenage Theater, 1968 May 14; Series 4 (Box 230, Reel 5)